Guide to the School of Engineering, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
School of Engineering, Yale University, student records
1917-1970
RU 224
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
34.5
The records consist of student files and registration cards maintained by the School of Engineering for students in the classes of 1917-1970, including records for students who left prior to graduation.
Yale University. School of Engineering
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 23-F (YRG 23-F), Student records of the Yale School of Engineering.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is partially restricted. See inventory for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of student files and registration cards maintained by the School of Engineering for students in the classes of 1917-1970, including records for students who left prior to graduation.
College students; Engineering students; Yale University -- Students; Yale University. School of Engineering
- Student records of the Graduate Division of the School of Engineering, 1930-1970; Accession 1995-A-023
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2046
- Registration cards for the Classes of 1920-1939, Accession 2002-A-005
  The materials are open for research.
  - 1920-1921 (Box 1)
  - 1922
    - A-Mi
    - Mo-Y (Box 2)
  - 1923-1924 (Box 3)
  - 1917-1918 (Box 4)
  - 1919, 1925-1926 (Box 5)
  - 1927-1929 (Box 6)
  - 1930-1933 (Box 7)
  - 1934-1937 (includes School of Engineering) (Box 8)
  - 1938-1939 (includes School of Engineering) (Box 9)
- Student registration cards, circa 1940-1965; Accession 2002-A-006
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2041
  - A-Clar (Box 1)
  - Clau-Gian (Box 2)
  - Gib-Kenn (Box 3)
  - Kenny-Moo (Box 4)
  - Schn-War (Box 6)
  - Was-Z; Special and transfer students (Box 7)
  - Classes of 1947m, 1952, 1953 (Box 8)
- School of Engineering and Yale College transcripts, 1946-1965; Accession 2005-A-119
- Transcripts and academic records of the School of Engineering, Graduate Division, 1930s-1960s; Accession 2005-A-121
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2045